A Guide to the Donald R. Griffin papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA164
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Publications, 4
  - Publications - By Others (Waring) (Box 29, Folder 221)
    Waring, Charles E., ed., Summary Technical Report of Division 17 NDRC, Vol. 3, Transition and Reception of Sounds Under Combat Conditions, Washington, D.C.: Office of Naval Research, 1946.